silkies.com 2017-12-27

# Terms: Privacy

**Privacy Policy**

**Privacy Policy Statement**

Sculptz and our brands, which include Silkies, Sculptz, Silkies Enriche, and PainVanish (collectively Sculptz, "our company," "we"), and our websites, 

[www.Silkies.com](http://www.silkies.com/), [www.Sculptz.com](http://www.silkies.com/), [www.SilkiesEnriche.com](http://www.silkiesenriche.com/) and [www.Painvanish.com](http://www.painvanish.com/) regard our customers' privacy as one of our most important values. We operate the Silkies.com website and our other sites for our individual brands (collectively and individually the “Site” or “Sites”). This policy applies ONLY to information about you that we acquire through the use of the Sites. We are committed to protecting your privacy whenever you use the Sites. This privacy policy was last updated on June 3, 2015 and is effective as of that date. 

**How do we protect your privacy?**

 **1\. What Information We Collect**

Whenever you visit the Site, we will recognize you by your domain name. When you order a product from Our Company at the Site, you will be providing personal information to Our Company. Personal information includes your name, telephone number, address, email and other information by which you can be personally identified. This personal information allows us to process and fulfill your orders as soon as possible and to notify you of your order status whenever you request it. If you use a credit card to make a purchase or join our program, the transaction and your credit card number and expiration date are stored on our server for archival purposes only. We will never disclose any of this information to any third party, except for the purpose of processing your purchase. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our Company makes use of cookies to enhance your Web viewing experience, to target advertising and marketing offers to your particular interests, and to avoid showing you duplicate ads. Third parties advertising on the Site may also use cookies. Cookies cannot be used to get data from your hard drive, your email or any other personal data about you. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you a chance to decide if you want to accept it or not. We contract with third parties to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. They may collect information about your visits to our website, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this website to target advertisements for our goods and services. This information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard techonology used by most major websites. Such third parties are not permitted to sell or share your personally identifiable information as part of this process. To “opt-out” from retargeting click here. Our company also collects usage information from visitors to the Site. We collect certain data on specific purchases. Usage information also includes how the Site is used, including the number and frequency of visitors to each page, the length of their stay, the domain names of browsers that visit the Site, time of day the Site was visited and other non-personally identifiable information. 

**2\. Use of Your Information**

Our Company believes that knowing more about you will enable us to serve you better. We use this information to personalize the content and services we offer to you. We will collect your email address when you give us that information. We do maintain a list of the email addresses our customers provide so we can provide customer service. From time to time, we may e-mail you with our new products, services and third party offers we think may be of interest to you. If you wish to have your name removed from our email list, you may "opt-out" of receiving email from us by writing to us at Customer Service, P.O. Box 402, Montoursville, PA 17754-0402 ... or calling us at 1-866-549-3051 or ... emailing us at [CustomerService@Silkies.com](mailto:CustomerService@Silkies.com). In addition, each email you receive will provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future emails. We reserve the right, from time to time, to re-contact former customers. If you supply us with your postal address, you may receive additional mailings from us at that address introducing our new products, offering different or improved products, or informing you about upcoming sales of new or existing products. If you supply us with your telephone number, you may receive a telephone call from us regarding any order you may place with us. You may also receive telephone calls from us regarding new products or information about upcoming special sales of existing products. If you do not wish to receive mailings to your postal address or telephone calls, you may "opt-out" of postal mailings and telephone calls by writing to us at Customer Service, P.O. Box 402, Montoursville, PA 17754-0402 ... or calling us at 1-866-549-3051 or ... emailing us at [CustomerService@Silkies.com](mailto:CustomerService@Silkies.com). Please note: we are not responsible for removing information from third party lists or entities with which you have engaged as a result of a third party e-promotion, banner or link on our Sites. We may also share your postal address with trusted third party marketing partners in order to alert you to products, services and special offers that may be of interest to you. You may "opt-out" of our sharing your information with third parties when you register on the Site or at any time by writing to us at Customer Service, P.O. Box 402, Montoursville, PA 17754-0402 ... or calling us at 1-866-549-3051 or ... emailing us at [CustomerService@Silkies.com](mailto:CustomerService@Silkies.com). You may change your mind at any time by writing to us at Customer Service, P.O. Box 402, Montoursville, PA 17754-0402 ... or calling us at 1-866-549-3051 or ... emailing us at [CustomerService@Silkies.com](mailto:CustomerService@Silkies.com). If you would like us to share your email address or phone number with trusted third party marketing partners in order to alert you to products, services and special offers that may be of interest to you; you may "opt-in" to sharing your information with third parties at any time by writing to us at Customer Service, P.O. Box 402, Montoursville, PA 17754-0402 ... or calling us at 1-866-549-3051 or ... emailing us at [CustomerService@Silkies.com](mailto:CustomerService@Silkies.com). You may change your mind at any time by writing to us at Customer Service, P.O. Box 402, Montoursville, PA 17754-0402 ... or calling us at 1-866-549-3051 or ... emailing us at [CustomerService@Silkies.com](mailto:CustomerService@Silkies.com). In addition, each email you receive will provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future emails. We may combine the information we have collected from you on the Site with other personally identifiable information (such as demographic information and past purchase information) available from our records and other sources. This information will be used to make our future marketing efforts more efficient. If you opt-in to sharing your information with third parties, they may also combine your information with other personally identifiable information available from their records and other sources to bring you offers of interest. We may disclose any information we have collected about you to law enforcement officials if necessary to comply with the law. In the event that all of our business assets are transferred, customer information will be one of the assets transferred. 

**3\. State-of-the-Art Technology**

When you place an order or access your account information, we use a state-of-the-art secure server to keep all your personal information -- including your billing and purchase information -- as secure as possible. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. We have put this privacy protection control system in place to help ensure that your personal data remains safe and private. However, we cannot guarantee the protection of your information from any actions taken by third parties that may unlawfully interrupt or access transmissions or private communications.

 **4\. Your Consent** By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Our Company in accordance with our Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to make changes to our Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Please check this page regularly for changes. If you have any comments or suggestions to improve our site or would like to review and/or update the information we have collected about you, please send an email to: [CustomerService@Silkies.com](mailto:CustomerService@Silkies.com), and be sure to include your account number. Please note that changes to your account status may not be effective immediately. 5. Links and Banners The Site may contain banners and links to third party Websites. We do not control and are not responsible for the information collection practices of the sites to which we provide links. We encourage you to review the privacy notices posted on those sites. The inclusion of a third party link or banner on our Sites does not imply endorsement by Our Company. 6. Opt-Out If you do not wish to allow us to use your information to provide you with the benefits described above, just let us know by writing to us at Customer Service, P.O. Box 402, Montoursville, PA 17754-0402 ... or calling us at 1-866-549-3051 or ... emailing us at [CustomerService@Silkies.com](mailto:Customer%20Service@Silkies.com). Be sure to tell us what type of communication you no longer wish to receive and give us your complete address and telephone number so we can remove your name from the lists we may use and/or share with other companies in the future. **YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS  
**  
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Sculptz who are California residents to request that we not disclose personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at Customer Service, P.O. Box 402, Montoursville, PA 17754-0402 or email us at [CustomerService@Silkies.com](mailto:CustomerService@Silkies.com). Please include "California Residents 3rd Party Opt-Out" on the envelope or in the subject line of your email. For all requests, please include your name, street address, city, state, and zip code.
